A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction (Accession 39607), 1974-2006., Extent: xx boxes. (Box 1-xx)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. W. E. Campbell), 1978-1979.
    - Superintendent's Study Groups, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Superintendent salaries, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Scott County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Shenandoah County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Smyth County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Southampton County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Stafford County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Suffolk, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Surry County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Sussex County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - T - General, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Tazewell County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Testing for students and teachers - Articles on, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Testing for students and teachers - Correspondence, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Title I Audit - Correspondence, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U - General, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U.S. Congress, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U.S. Commissioner of Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U.S. Commissioner of Education - Health Education and Welfare, Office of Civil Rights - Assurance and compliance with Section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - V - General, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Schools, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators (VASA), 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Council of Higher Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Education Association (VEA), 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Forum on Education (Dr. A. Perry Johnston, Director, VPISU), 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Manufacturing Association, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Public School Authority, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Public Telecommunications Council, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Virginia Beach, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - W - General, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Warren County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Washington County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Waynesboro, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Westmoreland County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - West Point, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Williamsburg, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Winchester, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Wise County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Wythe County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - X-Y-Z - General, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - York County, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Central Office, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Campbell, W.E., 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Cochran, W.H., 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Davis, Dr. S. John, 1978-1979. (Box 6a)
    - Orr, George S. - Proposed graduate program, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Director, Administrative Review - S. Barry Morris, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Federal Programs - Mr. Wildly, Associate Director, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - School Food Service - Mr. John Miller, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Program Development - Dr. R.L. Boyer, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Dept. of Education - Inventory of Personal Information, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Management Information Systems, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Director of Planning, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Research, Evaluation and Testing, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Administrative Field Services - Dr. E.B. Howerton, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Community Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Teacher Education - Mr. Wayland Jones, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Assistant Superintendent for Curriculum and Instruction - Dr. Carl L. Riehm, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Dr. Callie Shingleton, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Divisions of Sciences and Elementary Administration, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Driver Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Healtha and Physical Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Humanities and Secondary Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - History, Government and Geography, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Music Service, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Proprietary Schools, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Dr. N. Grants Tubbs, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Special Education - Mr. James Micklen, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - General Support Services - Dr. William Bosher, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Bureau of Teaching Materials, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Gifted and Talented, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Guidance Services, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - School Libraries and Textbooks, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Telecommunications, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Director, Title I - Dr. Sparks, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Dr. Melvin Garner, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Agricultural Education, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Administration and Finance - Mr. F. Brent Sandridge, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Basic School Aid - Mr. Hager, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Director of Finance - Mr. T.J. Bise, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Personnel, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Harry L. Smith, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Appropriations Committee, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Attorney General, 1978-1979. (Box 6b)
    - Civil Digest - Attorney General, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Children, Division of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Corporation Commission, State, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Employment Commission, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - General Services, Dept. of (Engineering and Buildings, Purchases and Supply), 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Emergency and Energy Services, State Office of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Governor's Office, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Governor's Office - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Lieutenant Governor, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Administration, Secretary of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Education, Secretary of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Human Affairs, Secretary of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - State Agency Group Luncheon, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Health Dept., 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Highways Dept., 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Justice and Crime Commission, Division of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Juvenile Court - Public School Task Force, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Legislative Services, Division of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Virginia Register Committee (Register of Regulations), 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Miscellaneous State Agencies, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Personnel Division, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Rehabilitative School Authority, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Transportation and Safety, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
    - Welfare and Institutions, Dept. of, 1978-1979. (Box 7a)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1979-1980.
    - A - General, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Administrative Review, Director, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - American Association of School Administrators (AASA), 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Appalachia Educational Laboratory, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Accomack County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Albemarle County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Alexandria City, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Amelia County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Amherst County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Appomattox County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Arlington County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Augusta County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - B - General, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Blood drive, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Bath County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Bedford County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Bland County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Botetourt County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Bristol City, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Brunswick County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Buchanan County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Buckingham County, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Buena Vista, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - C - General, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Career education, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Centex (Center for Excellence, Inc.), 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Central Office staff meetings, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Certificates of appointment, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Colleges and Universities - VPISU CETA information materials, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - , 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers / U.S. Dept. of Education - Conference, 1980 June. (Box 8a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers - Annual Convention, 1979 Nov. (Box 8a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers - International Education Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers - Directory and Policy Statement, 1979-1980. (Box 8a)
    - Campbell County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Cape Charles, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Carroll County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Charles City County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Charlotte County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Charlottesville, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Chesapeake, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Chesterfield County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Clarke County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Clifton Forge, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Colonial Beach, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Colonial Heights, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Covington, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Craig County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Culpeper County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Cumberland County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Code Commission, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Committee to assist in the development of guidelines for use of the National Teacher Examination, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Advisory Committee on Child Abuse and Neglect, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Committee on Declining Enrollment, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia State Special Education Advisory Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Developmental Disabilities Planning and Advisory Council, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Council on the Environment, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Commission on the Review of the Federal Impact Aid Program, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Council of Health and Medical Care, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Commission on Local Government, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Advisory Research Committee on Plans and Specifications for School Buildings, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Substance Abuse Advisory Council, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Advisory Council on Substance Abuse, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Telecommunications Study Commission, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Advisory Council for Vocational Education, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Community Education Advisory Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Indenpendence Bicentennial Commission, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Yorktown Bicentennial Committee, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Commissions and Committees - Virginia Council for the Deaf, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - D - General, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Danville, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Dinwiddie County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - E - General, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Education USA, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - F - General, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Fairfax City, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Fairfax County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Falls Church, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Fauquier County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Floyd County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Fluvanna County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Franklin City, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Franklin County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Frederick County, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - Fredericksburg, 1979-1980. (Box 8b)
    - G - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - General Assembly - House of Delegates, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - General Assembly - Senate, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - General Assembly - Fiscal impact statements, 1980. (Box 9a)
    - General Assembly - Legislative information, 1980. (Box 9a)
    - General Assembly - Legislative summaries, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Goals of public education, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Granville P. Mead Scholarship, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Giles County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Gloucester County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Goochland County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Grayson County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Greene County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Greensville County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - H - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Halifax County / South Boston, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Hampton, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Hanover County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Henrico County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Henry County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Highland County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Hopewell, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - I - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Isle of Wight, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - J - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - K - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - King George County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - King William County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - L - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Lee County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Lexington, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Loudoun County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Louisa County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Lunenburg County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Lynchburg, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - M - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Marsh and McClellan, Inc., 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Madison County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Manassas City, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Manassas Park, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Martinsville, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Mathews County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Mecklenburg County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Montgomery County, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - N - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - Northern Virginia Chapter NCAC (Autistic children), 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education - Conference, 1979 Oct. (Box 9a)
    - national Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1979-1980. (Box 9a)
    - New Kent County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Newport News, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Norfolk, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Northampton County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Northumberland County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - O - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - On Board, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Open House, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Orange County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - P - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Picnic - Annual, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Page County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Patrick County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Petersburg, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Poquoson, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Portsmouth, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Powhatan County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Prince Edward County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Prince William County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Pulaski County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - R - General, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Register of Regulations, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Report on Public Education in Virginia (1978-1979), 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Right to Read Program, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Radford, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Rappahanock County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Richmond County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Roanoke City, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Roanoke County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Rockbridge County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Rockingham County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Russell County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - S- General, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - State-Ed, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - State Departments of Education - Other states, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Superintendents' Advisory Council, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Superintendents' Study Groups, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Salem, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Scott County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Shenandoah County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Smyth County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - South Boston, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Southampton County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Stafford County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Staunton, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Suffolk, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Surry County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - Sussex County, 1979-1980. (Box 9b)
    - T - General, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Teachers reporting daily unencumbered planning period and duty free lunch period, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Tazewell County, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Testing (competency) for students and teachers - Correspondence, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U - General, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Congress - Correspondence, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Commissioner of Education, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Office of Education, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Bureau of Education for the Handicapped, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Office of Civil Rights (HEW) - Assurance of compliance with section 504 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Office of the Attorney General, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Campaign, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Secretary of Education, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education Weekly, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - United Givers Fund Campaign, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - United Way Campaign, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - V- General, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Association for Children with Learning Disabilities, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Association of Counties, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Association of Elementary School Principals (VAESP), 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators (VASA), 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Association of School Executives (VASE), 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Committee for Fair Impact Aid Funding, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Council of Community Colleges, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Council of Higher Education, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Council of Teachers of Mathematics, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia County Officials, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Forum on Education (Dr. A. Perry Johnston, Dir. VPISU), 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - virginia Education Association (VEA), 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia High School League, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Public School Authority, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Telecommunication Council, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - Virginia Beach, 1979-1980. (Box 10a)
    - W - General, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Warren County, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Washington County, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Waynesboro, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Westmoreland County, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Williamsburg, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Winchester, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Wise County, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Wythe County, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - X-Y-Z - General, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - York County, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Dr. S. John Davis - Correspondence, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Title IV-C Conference, 1979 Nov. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Minimum Competency Testing (Remarks to House Education Subcommittee), 1979 June. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Pupil Transportation - Who Needs It?, 1979 July. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Testing Conference, 1979 Aug. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Dedication of schools, 1979-1980. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - State PTA Convenction - Pass the Tarnex, 1979 Oct. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1979 Aug. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia State Distributive Education Conference, 1979 Aug. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Vocational Teachers Inservice Pre-School Conference, 1979 Aug. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Augusta County Pre-School Conference - What Do You Expect?, 1979 Aug. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Suffolk Public Schools PTA, Administrators and Central Office Staff - The PTA as a Social Organization, 1979 Sept. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Educational Research Association, 1979 Oct. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Vocational Association - Be Prepared, 1979 Oct. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Phi Delta Kappa Annual Banquet, 1979 Nov. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Clinch Valley College, Wise - Direction of Education in Virginia, A Perspective for the 80s, 1979 Dec. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Administrative Management Society - How Do You Spell Release?, 1980 Mar. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Council of Teachers of Mathematics - Math Teachers: An Endangered Species, 1980 Mar. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Title I Conference, 1980 Mar. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia State Leadership Conference - Campaign for Public Education, 1980 Mar. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Education Media Association, 1980 Mar. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - American Association of University Women, 1980 Apr. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - On Or About Instruction (Broadcast), 1980 Apr. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, 1980 Apr. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Middle School Forum, 1980 Apr. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Association of Educational Secretaries, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - James Madison University graduation address, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Symposium on Development of School / Community Mental Health Programs, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Christiansburg-Blacksburg Rotary Club, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Virginia Consortium of Social Studies Supervisors and College Educators, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Strengthening Instruction K-12, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Lee County Educational Forum (Radio interview), 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Indiana University of Pennsylvania - Graduation address, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Roanoke City School Board, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Phi Beta Kappa - A Different Perspective, 1980 May. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Fluvanna County High School - Graduation address, 1980 June. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Lake Braddock Secondary School - Graduation address, 1980 June. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - American Education Advisory Committee, 1980 June. (Box 10b)
    - Speeches - Conference on Coal Utilization: Potential for Public Schools, 1980 June. (Box 10b)
    - Neslon, Maggie S., 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Cochran, W.H., 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Manson, Jennifer, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)
    - Planning Advisory Council, 1979-1980. (Box 11a)